export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `Louis van Gaal mistakenly referred to which Manchester United player as 'Mike' in a press conference?`,
    answers: ['Michael Carrick', 'Chris Smalling', 'Nani', 'Van Persie'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: 'Chris Smalling',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `Who scored the winning goal for Manchester United in their 2-1 Champions League final victory in 1999?`,
    answers: [
      'Ole Gunnar Solskjaer',
      'David Beckham',
      'Gary Neville',
      'Ryan Giggs',
    ],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Ole Gunnar Solskjaer',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `Alex Ferguson famously kicked a boot at which player, injuring his eye?`,
    answers: ['Eric Cantona', 'Roy Keane', 'Patrice Evra', 'David Beckham'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'David Beckham',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `Manchester United broke their record transfer fee in 2016 when they paid £89.5 million for which player?`,
    answers: ['Harry Maguire', 'Juan Mata', 'Paul Pogba', 'Jodan Sancho'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Paul Pogba',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `The highest transfer fee ever received by Man Utd was £80 million in 2009 - for which player?`,
    answers: [
      'Cristiano Ronaldo',
      'David Beckham',
      'Ruud Van Nistelrooy',
      'Michael Owen',
    ],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `The famous 'Dab' dance move was invented by Paul Pogba and Jesse Lingard.`,
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `In Manchester United's 2008 Champions League final victory over Chelsea on penalties, who was the only Red Devils player to miss a spot-kick?`,
    answers: ['Nani', 'Anelka', 'Owen Hargreves', 'Cristiano Ronaldo'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `Who were Manchester United's opponents in the first game at Old Trafford?`,
    answers: ['Arsenal', 'Liverpool ', 'Derby County', 'Chelsea'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: 'Liverpool',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `Chesney Brown, a character in the British soap opera Coronation Street, had a Great Dane dog named after which Manchester United player?`,
    answers: [
      'Peter Schmeichel',
      'Eric Cantona',
      'Sir Bobby Charlton',
      'Denis Law',
    ],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Peter Schmeichel',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `Manchester United inflicted their biggest Premier League win - 9-0 - on which opponent in 1995?`,
    answers: ['Nottingham Forest', 'QPR', 'Ipswich Town', 'Arsenal'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Ipswich Town',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: `How many goals did Ashley Young score in Manchester United's 8-2 victory over Arsenal?`,
    answers: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'None'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Two',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: `Which player holds the record for most Man Utd appearances?`,
    answers: ['David De Gea', 'Michael Carrick', 'Ryan Giggs', 'Wayne Rooney'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'Ryan Giggs',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: `At 46 years, 281 days, which player was the oldest to ever appear for Manchester United?`,
    answers: ['Billy Meredith', 'Ryan Giggs', 'Michael Owen', 'Paul Scholes'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: 'Billy Meredith',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: `The players who progressed to the Manchester United first-team under Matt Busby were known as what?`,
    answers: ['The Red Devils', 'The Busby Babes', 'Red Army', 'Invincibles'],
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    correct: 'The Busby Babes',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: `Who scored the other two goals when Teddy Sheringham notched his treble against Southampton in 2000?`,
    answers: ['Andy Cole', 'Ryan Giggs', 'Paul Scholes', 'Denis Law'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Andy Cole',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: `In which year did Dwight Yorke score three of our six goals against Arsenal?`,
    answers: ['1999', '2000', '2001', '2002'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: '2001',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: `Who is the only player to score a Boxing Day hat-trick for United in the Premier League?`,
    answers: [
      'Wayne Rooney',
      'Robin Van Persie',
      'Dimitar Berbatov',
      'Ruud Van Nisterooy',
    ],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: 'Dimitar Berbatov',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: `And which Red has made the most appearances in the Champions League, with 151?`,
    answers: ['Paul Scholes', 'Wayne Rooney', 'Ryan Giggs', 'Gary Neville'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: 'Ryan Giggs',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: `The Reds hold the record for the longest run of unbeaten games in the competition. How long was that sequence, set between 2007 and 2009?`,
    answers: ['15 games', '20 games', '25 games', '18 games'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: '25 games',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: `Who was nicknamed 'Smudger'?`,
    answers: ['Steve Bruce', 'Sammy Mcllory', 'Alan Smith', 'Alan Stepney'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Alan Smith',
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: `In which year was Old Trafford opened?`,
    answers: ['1900', '1910', '1920', '1930'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: '1910',
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: `Can you name the architect of Old Trafford?`,
    answers: [
      'Archibald Leitch',
      'Archibald Montgomery',
      'Archibald Simpson',
      'Jonny Haynes',
    ],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Archibald Leitch',
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: `David Beckham scored 85 goals. How many of them were free-kicks?`,
    answers: ['14', '20', '26', '24'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: '26',
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: `How many times did Ole Gunnar Solskjaer score as a substitute?`,
    answers: ['9 times', '19 times', '29 times', '16 times'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: '29 times',
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: `In which year did Ryan Giggs score his last goal?`,
    answers: ['2011', '2012', '2013', '2014'],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: '2013',
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: `Who did Manchester United beat in the quarter final, to win the Champions League in 1999?`,
    answers: ['Real Madrid', 'Inter Milan', 'Barcelona', 'Ac Milan'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Inter Milan',
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: `Who scored the last goal of Ole Gunner Solskjaer reign as Manchester United manager?`,
    answers: [
      'Bruno Fernandes',
      'Cristiano Ronaldo',
      'Donny van de Beek',
      'Harry Maguire',
    ],
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    correct: 'Inter Milan',
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: `Which club knocked out Manchester United in the Third round of the FA cup under David Moyes?`,
    answers: ['Swansea City', 'Sunderland', 'Arsenal', 'Wigan Athletic'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Swansea City',
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: `Vidic made his debut and then first Premier League appearance against the same club. Which one?`,
    answers: ['Blackburn Rovers', 'Manchester City', 'Fulham', 'Portsmouth'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Blackburn Rovers',
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: `We beat Southampton 9-0 in 2020/21, but excluding the own goal, how many goalscorers did the Reds have?`,
    answers: ['Six', 'Seven', 'Eight', 'Five'],
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    correct: 'Seven',
  },
];

export const winningMultiplier = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10];
